A good friend to meet, MBC
What, there are so many people
Ah, but where is she?
uh
Hey Kim Ji-seong
What are you doing there? Why didn’t you get on board?
this traitor
They said they don’t use coins or anything like that.
Oh, that's the situation
Oh, so you ride together too.
I hate it there more than here
What if it's hell?
Hey, it's worse than the reality we live in
Where is hell? I hate it.
I won't go
child
The train will depart in a moment.
Dear passengers,
Please take a seat.
Please fasten your seat belt.
Hey, the train is leaving.
I'm not going
Oh, I'm not going, I'm not going.
Hey hey Jisong, Jisong
Ah
Welcome passengers
our train
of labor
Miserable whose values are not respected
I started from reality
Sister, what is this?
Cosplay while our train is running
There is a slight risk of injury
injured
Ah ah hot
Ah
uh
Twenty bite marks
I'm already bitten. I'm bitten.
But it's better that way
That guy over there
three thousand
And that woman over there, Sacheon
And uhhh
Why are you doing this? Are you okay?
Oh oh five thousand
I just paid 5,000 dollars. What should I do?
Sister, please stop. There is an injured person here.
You can't stop
You can't stop because it's not possible. That's right.
Let's go to the end together. Yes, I agree.
Yes I agree I agree
I agree
I agree I agree
Our train has one person
Without even wanting to leave, the final
destination
I'm planning to go to the moon
I hope you hold on tight.
The result of every choice
Don't forget your heart
When like this
Lady and Gentleman
Fighting, I barely made it
Let's all shout together
let's go to the moon
To the Moon
To the Moon, a little more, a bigger touch
Tudhoon
Todhoon open the door
Gaya
Oh, what are you doing? I told you to open the door.
Ah
Hey, that's right, mom decided to come.
Mistress
Come to work mom
Look
It's the threshold
There is a threshold
Awesome, it’s really going up
Why are you looking at me like that?
uh
Oh no, no, how about this?
It's useful
mom is my daughter
I don't think I was very bad at raising it.
How hard would you like to live?
I've lived in houses like this
Great job my daughter
What kind of kid do you have this much?
Oh, I'm going to eat and then go.
Cook it roughly, yeah
But what are these boxes?
Oh, I'm going to throw that away.
Ah, those books I don’t read
Photos from when I was young
No, why throw away the photo?
Ah two
If you don't have time, just hang it on the wall.
Uh oh
uh what
Oh no
No, no, mom, Mochira, no, no.
No no no no no
No, baby, why why why are you like this?
Oh, what are you doing, mom?
What if I call that guy mochi?
This isn't really my home
Oh, this isn't really scratched.
Oh this
people hammer sound
You probably didn't hear that.
Oh what should I do
Ah, why are you so scared of this?
Let's eat
Wow
Really yes
me
Please create a laptop ID.
I also use laptops and things like that.
Oh my
Play some music while you drive
I woke up and it wasn't good, um
Uh, what should I do for my profile picture?
Oh, check out that album.
There are a lot of pictures
Yeah
This wasn't taken from the TV screen
Well, it's all like this
No, why should I make this my profile?
You're pretty, hey
At first glance
Doesn’t it feel like you really went there?
Oh, it's not like that at all.
Oh look at this
This is a home shopping screen shot.
Ah, I'm so busy I don't have time to go anywhere.
It's good to feel like this
What to do when you're busy
Oh, Mom, let’s get some air in our noses too.
What is there in the fall?
I go out to see autumn leaves and things like that.
Oh my
That's from a certain Daegamtaek.
Hey, everyone adapts to their own circumstances.
I'm living
Being greedy for something that isn't mine
It's not that magic trick.
Give it to me
mountain
Good, okay
Wow
It's pretty
Yeah
part time job
It's the weekend
When playing, keep the coin bullet close
You have to earn it
You too
Don't think about spending money unnecessarily.
Do some part-time work
Jisung too
What is a part-time job?
he is now
It will be folded in half haha.
I'm on a real continent
If it weren't for the miraculous face
I won't do that at least once haha
It's been 200 days with your boyfriend.
Today too she
It means you're crossing the border.
Hey, what a pure thing.
Can't you perform?
Even the angsty pop star is better than him.
I'll stop by
But what's going on?
My voice isn't very good
just
I feel terrible
Hey, if you drink on a day like this, you’ll have an accident.
I drink for no reason
I remember drinking and the film cut out.
It doesn't fly
don't do it
Go home early and leave early
Just wipe it and go to sleep.
Hey, a guest has arrived.
Oh yes, the person who said Kora is hurt.
Wow
daughter daughter
daughter
That customer
I can't handle a car like this.
After the accident, it's over there.
Taken to a coal mine
Even if I do this for the rest of my life, I won't be able to repay it.
Oh, that's right, I'm sorry about this.
Ah
Ah, I will give it to you in the future.
Comrade Gabosidio, close the door.
What are you doing, Lee Mojiri bastard?
IC
A glass of beer at a karaoke bar
It'll be okay
Issi ah
I will never receive foreign car cologne again.
I was so nervous. I'm a bad person. Do you want to shoot me?
Wow
I hope
Someone drives a supercar like that?
Who is like this
Oh, riding a crowded bus
kid really
Ah ah
I really don't want to go to work
So how do you make money?
I don't even use coins
Ai’s real coin
I'm tired, really, sister.
Hey, I hope you become rich. Thank you.
What
What do you want to do when you become rich?
Yeah hey
When you become rich
become richer
The more rich you become, the more
become even richer
You have to think
He first thought about buying it.
Try it quickly, what do you want to do?
Well, what if I become rich?
Once it's all done
I'm going to throw away the toothpaste right away.
Ah, the toothpaste that doesn’t come out every morning
What I wanted to give
blood pressure so hard
I feel like it's going to explode
Oh and
I won't even lick the Yoplait lid.
You have to be rich to do that much flex.
Haha uh
Oh, I'm here, sister.
Ah bye bye
Oh, what are you talking about?
Ah, what does he want to do when he gets rich?
When my sister becomes rich
But where
There's no burning smell, huh?
When I get rich, I'll hit the wall
I'll hit the nail in first.
nail
Oh, you're on a charter, right?
You can't nail it
Wow, if you girls are that rich,
What I want to do
It's barely like that.
Then what do you want to do?
About me
In the Han River
Penthouse overlooking
500 won per bottle on the highest floor
I'm going to drink a quick dragon.
And with my dad
I'm talking on the phone.
Dad ex
without love
I really don't want to get married.
Please leave me free.
And the luxury item I was holding in one hand.
The white buffalo is on the main wave
Throwing it like this
I'm talking about
ha
Life is so empty
Still, didn’t it get a little warm?
Ah, I guess spring has come
Oh, really, don't ignore me.
Hey, I guess there's a fire
over twenty people
Smoke inhalation or injury
This is reporter Kim Soo-young.
Around 2 am this morning
Nine-story scale in Gwanak-gu, Seoul
There was a fire at the motel.
When the fire broke out, the guests
Forty people evacuated
Seven people inhaled smoke during this process.
people were taken to hospital
Oh, that suddenly
The secret ship rang and smoke came out.
Oh, what are you so surprised about?
Clothes properly too
Change your clothes and just do this
I ran out. What was it?
Yes, I got drunk after tearing off that hat.
That's not Dahyun, unnie.
Hey, what are you doing drinking again?
Doing things
I'm really going crazy
Yes, yes, this is Mr. Shitball.
That's right
no
How do I do this?
How can I see you so clearly
Wow
If you mosaic this, you will get this
Do it carefully
what is this
This is roughly like this like this
I can see all your faces like this
Ah ugh
Wow, there were a lot of comments.
Mosaic's Betrayal
Motelier real taxidermy hehehehe
The feeling of a workplace that wants to be set on fire
I know it so well
Because of me the fire
It's not something you want to complain about.
no no
Ah ah ah
But what happened to the team leader?
Check out the morning news
no
The company's bulletin board was posted.
Not a hoppang
Share this post
Yes, it's your company bulletin board.
Lady, you crazy bastard
I threw a punch
don't worry too much
The administrator already deleted it
Specific slander is not allowed.
The number of views was barely there.
But Mr. Tongko
I have to go to get married.
But why
No this
A woman who never got married
My face was sold like this, hmm
I ask my boyfriend to get married quickly, yeah.
Oh, that
I was with my boyfriend
No.
Then
who is it
Who is it?
Why don't you say something and jump out?
Who is that big?
I made a mistake, yeah
I really won't tell you
Please give me some hints
Are you stuck in a string?
What line to give
A money line, a money line, a blood line
Oh right
My sister was a blood pervert.
What a pervert
hey i just
I don't like blood
hardened by labor
You like blood
Well, for example, yeah
Looks like it's going to be in an extreme job
He worked hard
I lived
A man who proves himself with thick veins
Isn't it sexy?
Come visit me no matter what
The tenacity to not starve
You can see it
ha
crazy
dog is sexy
I like sexy too
Well, I'm good at perseverance
Hey
It's because you don't know
I am a person like my father
Because he is a sincere man
This is so sexy
A person who likes being sincere
Why do I use coins?
My sister also earns diligently.
Then the ideal and reality are different, right?
Even though my reality is sincere
Even if you do it, it's only to the limit.
coin-like
Some special measures were needed.
So last night
That man is also sincere
Was he the sexy type?
Was he that type?
That's
my privacy
Oh this
I think I'm going to hit it with a frying pan.
Mr. Lee
I was just drunk and got into an accident once.
That's right, there's nothing more to do with me.
I don't think so
If this happens
Isn’t there more left here?
Mistress
But why
Was the woman alone being interviewed?
The man
I guess I didn't do the interview because I was embarrassed.
Hehehe
Actually, the woman is so cute.
That's about average
Ah, until now
There aren't many views, Mr.
These miscellaneous things
What are you doing?
Oh this
These people are talking nonsense, so why not just leave it at that?
I will post a rebuttal comment
Uh huh
A person's appearance
It is mature to judge someone based solely on their body.
It's not an attitude
Especially sex life
To a very personal area
Please refrain from making teasing remarks.
It hurts hahaha
uh reply here
Reply Turn off the frame here and here
What is ttttak ttttag?
The truth is, old man, fuck off.
Oh, such a sharp bastard
Like this
Whenever I see kids getting upset, my frontal lobe
It melts gently
Why is my frontal lobe melting?
Making fun of me makes my frontal lobe melt
They say it's as fun as it is
Haha kid
I'm in the mood to get angry by now
It must have been 2,000 won more expensive.
This is my sister
Hit the bone with facts and turn into pure tongue
They said they applied it
What is this
suddenly leaves grandmother photo
Why did you come up
I feel frustrated like my sister's sweet potato.
This and mine too
Oh no, why are the comments so fast?
you need to take your time
stop uh
Here, here, here and there, the incisor line
Incisal line Incisal line here
Oh it's true
What is the incisor line?
This
Please don't leave comments below.
It's sick, no, what is that?
Okay, I don't want to know, okay.
What did people do during the beeper era?
Okay, I'll do it.
This
I again
Various S&S and various
Salary earned through many years of training
Lupine is Kim Ji-sung.
Are you proud?
First, write a comment
We need to figure out his identity first.
size report
very just
Talking about leaving my heart behind
I really
Grind, grind, grind what?
Married twice, married three times
Are you out of your mind?
Why did you throw someone away?
what does that mean
Oh my, did you change your face?
you got married a while ago
Marriage was like this
But why am I being abandoned?
I uh
tell me honestly
What is a person and what is a fictional character?
Ha Il-in haha
Oh, you're right mom
The ID is just right.
that
It’s true that I changed your profile picture too.
Oh no then
Yes my daughter
I sat down after being scolded, but I turned my back.
They say you have a lover too?
These two bastards
Someone else's daughter goes to a motel
who built a motel
What do they care?
Oh, stop talking about motels.
This is
Why do you keep getting so irritated?
Oh, I'll take care of tomorrow
I told you not to worry
Oh my
Okay, okay.
But you last night
I was with my friends
Playing with friends all night long
That's it
I think it's strange
I'm not hurt
Hey, are you hurt? You little girl.
Okay then hang up
Ah
um
Wow crazy
Since when have you been here?
Why aren't you answering the phone?
Oh this
Where did you go?
No this
Where did you go? I guess I dropped something. Yeah, what?
Oh, something is missing.
Where did you go
It's a concept
yes
You have to look at your boss and say hello.
such a concept
You know,
I dropped it
I think it's okay, hello
hello i see
You have become a patient.
How did you become famous?
What happened
yes what how
Can I at least give you an autograph?
There was no relationship in a bad way.
You are the only one out of a million antis
I think it's my mom.
why are you so angry
Oh why
Eavesdrop on other people's phone calls.
I have a question
Can I ask
uh
um
That's Dr. Han
This is a company
No matter how boss you are
on duty
Why are you doing this?
I hope you'll refrain from doing so.
after work
my personal
Interfering with my private life
But what about growing it?
Wow wow
Wow wow what is this
Wow ah what should I do
Ah
I'm glad. Oh, let it go, let it go, let it go, let it go.
Wow ah go away
Oh where did you go? where did you go?
Where did you go? Where did you go?
Where did you go
Wow Mr.
Why don't you try catching a big one?
Well ah
Follow my eyes, tuna
The motel fire incident aired this morning.
Complaint about the interview scene
Mosaic of ordinary people
processing is urgent
While infringing on portrait rights
serious personal information
Leading to exposure
Is this a true story?
If this mistake keeps repeating itself
news
Breed loses the respect of viewers
it's time
It's a problem
thank you
If it continues like this, stop loss
Real beat irrefutable
recognition
The ban on sweet potatoes is expected to be quickly corrected.
A flag was posted on the bulletin board of the broadcasting station.
mosaic
Do it again properly and comment
Stop it
uh
There is nothing that can be done for those who have already seen it
Emergency fires need to be put out
I love you Eunseong Kang
Anyway, I threw that kid away yesterday.
What's the point of swearing all by yourself?
What is the right thing about veins?
Blood is widespread in the world.
crazy
You don't know whose bloodline this is
From the first time
Seo Kang-Jun in turn
Jeong Ye-in, Jung Yong-hwa, and Lee Min-ki
For reference, the last blood line is
It's our wale
why
Why did you engrave your name on something that was work?
I have to mark it as mine.
It happens, I'm angry
Sculptors work
Engraving your name
Calm down?
Where do kids like you travel?
If you go there, it is a treasure or cultural property of that country.
Scribble like that
Yeah
What is it
What kind of memory is this?
Oh my
hello
This is News Breed reporter Kim So-young.
Contact us regarding follow-up actions
You wrote down your wish
The video posted on the Internet
upload all
I stopped
I apologize separately to the parties involved.
We will contact you
Yes, I would appreciate it if you could.
Then
I think it's resolved, so I'll stop now.
Are you not my mother on earth?
who
It was in my reporting file a while ago.
This is reporter Kim So-young.
I covered the bus accident at the daycare center.
I still have your number
that
Follow up with your father
I contacted you a few more times while reporting.
How have you been, mother?
Ah
yes
I just
We have the best blood.
No, I don't know because it's a mosaic.
Hey, that's right.
That's not Dahye unnie.
Um, Mr. Jisung, what does that mean?
the news that
You were talking about mosaics.
No, that’s right, singer Choi Kyu
There was a scandal this time
Ah, but
actress mosaic
It's been processed so I don't know who it is.
Ah, me again haha
That's called Minseok.
Oh, that's not Park Sam.
Oh no.
No, I just saw that you were wearing clothes.
I heard it was Sam
What do you know, Jisung?
Ah, no way, now
While talking about love and fashion, I
You're ignoring me
Aha
It's me
You can tell whose bloodline it is just by looking at it.
know
Well, it's at that level hehehe
What did you say
Would you like to bet 10,000 won with me?
ok
Now look here.
If you look at this article
The woman recently appeared in a drama.
Appeared in his twenties
woman learn
It is done
Speaking of dramas that ended recently,
terrestrial cable
Total including web dramas
There are six
Yeah, twenties
There are a total of four works in which female actors appeared.
It's a dog, then
on board the dragon
A total of four actors will appear.
Now here
mosaic on photo
untreated woman's cuff
Let’s take a look
Hey, this isn’t a bracelet.
It's a hair tie
What
When I saw it from a distance, I thought it was a bracelet.
Well, that could be it.
This season at Botaega Bonetti
Limited product
If so
The suspect had enough money to tie his hair back.
Must be a long person
Ha, then it's one of two things.
Heh, I see clear evidence.
The ring this woman is wearing here
This, this, this, this, this
Rosiely Ofrom this season
It's a diamond ring
The group with Mr. Insera
Rosiely Ambassador
I'm active
Look, I guess I got it through sponsorship, hehe.
So
The main character of this scandal is Min Se-ra.
I can assure you that Mr.
Jisong sees this
ha
This is my wannabe item
Is it because I looked for the picture so much?
riding the highway
I can see it as I go.
Oh, I guess Minji is really here.
Here's a picture of the mother and child's backbone.
Oh my
Wow Jisung is really amazing
No, how do I know this?
Oh, it's no big deal haha
Just give me 10,000 won
Oh my, that ring
This is the same one that Min Seol-ah is wearing.
No, yes
Huh, that's right
Oh my, that's right
I didn't even know I was wearing it
Oh, sir, this is really expensive.
But it's expensive
Still, whatever
It's not something I can't handle
Oh so pretty
Wow
Wow, Ji Seong-shin is a bit creepy.
Yours too
things that are not
how are you so good
Now
Hehehe
It's not like I'm looking at people, it's obvious
He's wearing those pants
Why do you pretend not to know when you have it?
Make a person's head and make me laugh
That's okay, it's really not funny.
Jisongah Slowly
If you laugh but it’s not funny
What does that mean?
no that person
Why are you touching me like this?
Oh, why do you keep calling people evil?
The person who feeds the baby
Why are good people angry?
No, that's not it
uh
Oh, you were here.
Jisung, may I help you?
你好我是住在你的同事吴钟奎
The truth is, the truth is true.
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good
Um Oh Dae-nim
Do you know how to speak Chinese?
I think you're doing very well.
Oh that that
I worked at the Chinese branch until the year of production.
I'm working
I don't need to learn Chinese to work
I can't help it
Oh yes, but don’t misunderstand.
uh what am i
Mr. Jisung
I can't give up
I keep trying to get in trouble
I'm not just saying that
something
I want to help you even a little bit
Yeah, why is it so short?
yes no
Our miserable and sad feelings
Why is the explanation so short?
Ah
That intelligence
It's okay, cheer up
No and why does he pity me
What is it? What did you say?
Oh that's just
I don't have money
Mr. Jisung’s pride has been shattered.
It happened like this
It's explained briefly
Ah ah
Oh, I see.
That explains it that way.
That's right
pride
Gaebaksal
uh
This product
These days
There was a good response from S&S.
The display location is a bit disappointing.
Oh, I see.
Placed in the main passage
can you please request
third party
I was pushed out because of a promotional product.
next week
Let me talk again.
These days, they say it's a battleground for fights at the stalls.
There are a lot of them
Still, the sticks are selling well.
It was a bit easier to breathe.
But Dahee
Maybe
Date Dr. Han
yes
No, why suddenly?
Ah before
headquarters
The two employees who entered
I saw you there
So it suits you so well
Just in case haha no
Oh and
It was just me and Dr. Han.
I have no enemies
There are so many people during the meeting.
Right
Yes uhhh what haha uh
Ah then that's it
These visuals are so unique.
Even though there were many people, only two caught my eye.
Kang Dong-won, a civilian bachelor
Feels like heaven and earth
No, what are you saying?
But Dahye, I really have no thoughts.
With Dr. Han
I think you'll suit it really well
Well I don't know
to the company
There are really people targeting Dr. Han.
There's a lot, that's right
No way, Dahye
Mr. Da-hye too.
What is it
Is it true that even you are like that?
Unfortunately,
my style is
Dr. Han
Because they are not the same person
Haha, you are so clear.
Even if I meet a useless brat
It's rotten inside
That Dahye
Are you okay? Yes, what is it?
That aha from earlier
Oh, I'm talking about Dr. Han.
Oh, I'm okay.
Oh, it's me
What are the eyes
It's not on the soles of my feet.
The two of us don't
I know for sure that it’s a fitting picture.
How could I get hurt haha oops
Ah, me too
Green is the same color
Sailors stand together
I know you wrote it
Why don't you know
Well, I'm not
I don't think you know
That's not it
new product
You asked for the list by tomorrow.
Are you okay with that alone?
Ah
Oh that
They say a strong negativity is a strong positivity.
Maybe
Dahye is also greedy for Dr. Han.
Oh no, no
Oh, I'm sorry.
It was a joke, but it wasn't me.
Oh, there's nothing to be sorry about
Yes, we've reached all the stops here, right?
Hey, hurry up and go in first.
yes yes
Ha Jeong Dahye really
Ha, what's your problem?
It has to be like this. Is this the best?
About me
Living in a penthouse
donville doll
Because I want to drink
I want to become rich
I thought it was
Yeah, that's not the only reason.
I need to buy a ring too.
Here
Than assistant manager
Much prettier and much more
I'll buy something shiny
so just
Pick your nose
I'm going to press it down, are you a crow?
Why do you always
like that
They only look for pretty and shiny things
sister
I need to say that again.
It's okay, you don't have to.
I have a painful past
Since I was young
kinda
There was something special about the sisters.
Since it's Dog Day, why not buy some chicken?
You know I searched and put it in.
What is it
Hey
That's right
Hey, did you see it?
this ring
Yesterday, Hyori unni joined in the breakup.
It came out, right?
Oh really really so pretty
where did you buy this
No, how much is it?
Is this real gold or not?
Oh my real sister
I always liked pretty things.
Well maybe
Maybe it was because I was born with an aesthetic sense.
There was another reason too
At that time, our house was completely
It was a garbage dump.
My father is mainly involved in business.
You are abroad
Mom was very lonely alone.
Then you found a place to put it.
That's why
It was a pseudo.
If you think about it, my life
That's when the creed was created.
I promised myself every day that someday, when I grow up,
my life
I'll give you only pretty things
Such smelly trash
Expensive things that smell good
Just those things
That it will fill my life
ah ah ah ah sorry
But
Mom Mom is the leader
I chased after them and left the house.
mom
The only family left is my father.
well
Even my dad is criticizing me for betrayal.
Why do you quit your job?
Why do you donate?
The offense of martial arts
I came empty handed
Life is about going empty-handed
I'm leaving this body behind too.
who is the card
Who owns the house?
Oh, you're with me, dad.
Don't go
Dad
really
It's not a strange story.
Kim Ji-seong's childhood left only with scars
I really can't listen without crying
um
tears
I can listen to it without it, I just drank alcohol.
Yes if you do it
regular drink
This is the alcohol
Do I have to cry every time?
Get down um
One more drink
So
I need to make money
You have to earn money to relieve your pain
It won't heal
If we play some coins together, I'll be like this
What did I do?
Coins and autographs are the same
You can also see
can touch
I don't even know if it's real or not
People who fall for it even though it has no substance
There really is no answer
Hey
Then earlier
That 1.25 million won ring
What is the answer?
If you buy that expensive thing, you will find the answer.
uh ring
She was pretty
I can't do it
I guess
That child
my
I think I put it on my finger.
I'm going to try plugging it in.
Let's go buy a ring
Oh, I'm going to buy a ring.
Wow let's go
Let's go buy a ring, hey, let's go out
Wow, just sit back and eat all of this.
sit sit sit sit sit
Oh, sit down.
Seeing it
I will go if I can
Hey kid, come late
Wow, you bastard
There's a fuss just because I couldn't use it
I really can't do it alone
That's right
In the first place
I wish I hadn't been greedy
uh
That's right
Because I'm greedy for what I can't have
Pride fades away with pride
The heart doesn't get hurt at will
What is it about Jisung? Is it about you?
what's wrong with you
What does the owner say?
Oh, call me, I'll fill the sea and come back
What
uh
What kind of memory is this?
Oh what
Oh no no no
Wait a minute
I got off work
Now in my private life
It might be time to touch it
Let's talk
Let's take a break and see you in an hour.
It's a work, it's a work of art
I need to write something down here.
name let him feel that flame
Ha, you can’t wash it.
You can't release the squadron.
No, what?
I can't solve anything
Oh sister
You hang up, I'll call you later.
Don't wash and wait.
I'll be there right away
Wait a minute, wait a minute
Wait, wait, I'm sorry.
sorry
Uncle stop
Man, please stop for a moment. Hey, me.
ha
How have you been, mother?
I'm doing well
how do i
salty
How are you? It’s pretty.
It looks real haha
Even if it doesn't go well
It's absurd, we're close, yeah
Wow
Hey, you're really sick. I'm sick. I'm sick.
Hey you idiot
This is
What if I search for coupons?
He's doing 20%
Really, what will he do?
Visitor Registration Application
Please write
Visitor registration
Ah, but
I really
I went up for a moment and then
I'll come down right away
This too soon
You can write it
Oh yes
yes
Here
Please enter your vehicle number
I came by subway
Please wait a moment
yes
Please check visitors
Oh, you are very kind.
Just me alone
You can go, but the elevator is for residents.
Because it’s for exclusive use.
You cannot use it without a card.
Oh yes
Oh that
thirty seven
I heard it was on the 20th floor.
Officetel pass at the lobby
Take it and go to the elevator.
You have to ride it
Yes, where else should I stop by?
The vehicle number is missing.
It's a relief ship.
They said they came on a relief ship.
Yes, I understand.
ha
Oh, what kind of immigration process are you going through?
Ah
No, what kind of bastard
It's hard to get into the house like this.
Ah
It was hard, but you really came.
I said let's meet outside, so I went all the way home
Ah, that's right
Are you going to wash now?
Can I help you?
Hey, that's me
Making hot noises like this again
I'm here to help.
Oh it's okay
Hey, I'm uncomfortable.
Oh, it's okay
My child's arm is like this
No, it hurts
Ah, driver
Ah
uh
Ah ah
Oh thank goodness
ha
thank you heavenly father
I will live a good life from now on
Please stay tuned
What are you doing? Ah yes
Ah
It's nothing
Ah, I guess I misunderstood something.
Oh, this is a question.
Yes, you were mistaken.
The number one national treasure is Sukremun.
Mine is jjimkong art bloodline
It's not a sexy explosion, yeah
No, why is this on that arm?
Oh, erase it
Oh I don't like it
No, please delete it quickly.
No, I have this as proof
How hard did it take to preserve it?
Oh, what kind of murderer are you catching?
Why do you leave evidence?
If you don't leave it
You're going to pretend like you don't know again
I'm a fool alone
I didn't mean to make it like that.
no that's
ha
What was hot that night was
Was it just for me?
Oh, what kind of thing?
Baby, what about that night?
It was just a drunken night.
How about
If you take care of the mixing
Titler of this house
Let's eat tuna
thank you
What is this, why is this reaction like this?
What is it
If you've heard the song, do you like it or not?
There has to be an answer, right?
this is my answer
Is eating tuna the answer for you? Yes.
Hey, you must be like that
hanging on the wall
Should I live while signing?
I think you are this expensive
When you buy it, put it on the receipt
It was the coolest time to sign autographs.
this is my answer
Juman, you
This line
With metal rock
Folk rock seems a bit unfamiliar.
Are you a pervert?
It's not like I haven't done anything
I just tried it
I haven't even tried it
Even though I messed up violently
Why is the road like this
I'm trying to write and make music again.
It's fun to fail
It's so thrilling when you get hurt.
my music
still
Someone who remembers and likes me
There should be
Even if it hurts that much, it's okay
Isn’t it worth trying again?
Jiwooya
From now on, repeat after me. What is it?
I don’t buy jade flooring and I don’t read newspapers.
What is that?
Then you
That person
What to me
They even tried to sell jade flooring.
no
Maybe he's preaching
as a friend
I'm like this because I don't want to lose you
music is just
Do it as a hobby
Ah
Chef, here’s your belly fat
mainly a plate
I would like more please
Yes hello
Oh, I was working earlier.
I didn't avoid my child's phone call.
It's a line
Oh, what kind of line is this? I hate it.
Oh, I don't like being picked on at my school.
Oh I really hate it
I really hate me
child
If you're going to stop talking like that
Why did you call me?
Mom, I’m only going to stay for a long time now.
I'm thinking of quitting my job.
For this long
I wish I could have gone
That
Now I'm going to start playing music again.
Take this opportunity to go all in on music
I'm going to give it a try
says
cut off like this
What do you do when you talk on the phone?
Wow
Wow awesome
Wow wow my jackpot
Oh you know my song
no how can i sing
Let’s just look at who it is, okay?
Let's just see who it is
um
Excuse me, I'm from here.
uh
I was sorry last time
There's something I'm a little angry about.
um
Oh, but I didn't do anything well either.
It wouldn't have been a big deal to do that to that fan.
I'm a fan, Dahye Jeong.
You're my fan
Ah
But that
Rather than being a fan of Dr. Han
It's me
When I was young
On a program called Maeal of Love
I've been out
The house is in complete ruin
But then
VCR introducing the story of our house
After the video ended,
Because the doctor sang
remember that
Uh uh ah
That stage was a mess.
It's not ruined.
I'm so nervous
At that time, there was probably a stage in front of me
Was it TVXQ?
It must have been like that.
At that time, girl fans told me
It was so cold back then
I liked it, I liked it, yes
I was there at that time
I was eighteen
Oh my house is ruined
the tv
Selling your face with me
Actually, I was embarrassed.
Oh, of course
I am
It was mosaic-processed.
Still, uh
Still
I wonder what if someone recognizes me
I really thought my life was a mess
that day
Seeing Dr. Han
It's okay
yes
I guess I'm not the only one who feels embarrassed.
That person must be just like me.
Like comrade knowledge
Since then
Our house collapsed twice more.
Every time
I gained strength while listening to Dr. Han’s song.
It was like that when I took the exam again.
uh
It was like that when I broke up with Cheonan-chin.
What
As I keep listening to the song
It was good
I look like a double head, but should I sing a warm song?
Ah
If you feel offended, I apologize
ok
yes
Oh my
It’s been a while since I received a compliment
Because I like it
Oh my, why are your eyes like this?
Oh my music
someone
It's so great to be saved
I love it so much
Salvation
Wow, why is it so unfair?
It's so crazy good
But if you make this mistake
It won't work
Ah
It's okay
Even if you make a mistake
Maybe
If you want to sell jade flooring
yes
let's just buy one
For reference
I am not at fault in this situation.
So does the news
Mr. Dahye
I got hurt while trying to save you.
Dahye is alone during this treatment.
It was an interview.
I came running as soon as the treatment was over.
I haven't even received a call
Could it be that I really avoided it?
No, of course
Ah
I think you're going to nail it. Yeah.
Oh yes
The picture frame fell off
It's like this
What is it, Dr. Han?
Hang your clothes on the living room wall
capable of driving
Even though I have a dick
I am
If you nail it to the living room wall, it's a big problem.
Because I don't exist
So please think about it.
Like me, you have no money or support.
What I have
This person from this company has no problem
If you say you slept
What will people say
It's a good thing they don't call it a flower snake.
uh no one
I don't think you'd call it a flower.
You don't know that
Yes ah
I did
Very little interest in Dr.
Even if you have it, others will see it as just
It's just greed
So
I made a mistake that day.
That's right
Maybe
Ah
While walking down the street
raise
A fierce-looking woman with a crazy haircut
I think it will come if you catch it.
yes
Because my mother came and went
I'm doing music again
Who blew that nonsense?
You left the house completely destroyed.
no what is that
Well, it's because of me. No.
I mean, I'm jealous.
Always baby
I also have a mother who takes my side
boss
The courage that Paldu displays is also wonderful.
Hey, give it a try
Dahye Jeong
A person who has more than me
So
don't avoid me
over and over again
I'm greedy
I want to become rich
When you become rich
better than now
I want to have good things
and i
enjoy it all
I'm a qualified person
I want to be confident
I want to be as greedy as I want
no more
I don't want to stop
Let's get started
Ah
Licking the lid and eating is an instinct.
Now you get it
The one who perseveres until the end wins.
The loser goes to karaoke
I'm shooting
Now, get ready.
start
By the way
Is it a secret until the end?
What was your big mistake?
no adult
Men and women are in trouble
I heard you did colleri
what is that
It's such a big secret
That's right
I'm my mother's pseudo-sindugo
Everything that happened to my father
I woke up and got hit
Just believe in something too
Is there anything you can trust in Korea?
What, Yeonwoo and Yunu?
Chinunim, Dr. Han
Hey, why is Dr. Han appearing there?
Dr. Han
ha
I really lost with Dr. Han.
Really
Huh no how
How did I come across this doctor?
Are you drunk?
Ah
no
I'll come to my senses once in a while
I've done it before
Oh, but it's because of that guy's light string
Then now
What happens next?
Yeah
what's going on
no
that
What will the future look like?
So uh
Even if you tell me to break up and run away
Throwing a stroke and adding water
Will a test horse appear?
Or what
I'm currently studying abroad in Paris, but...
Oki, who will be making a comeback in Korea soon
one hundred and sixty-eight centimeters
Long straight hair weighing 48 kilograms
Dr. Han's
Is first love appearing?
Oh hey
That first love
Even Jeon Ji-hyun can do it haha.
He's fucked, no
I am Jeon Ji-hyun
I will try to reach an amicable agreement with you.
What is this serious attitude?
You don't say you're giving up
Is it love?
Oh, it's love
It's not like that
ha
me
I put 10 million won more in the coin.
Because I pierced the barrel
I'm going to give it a go
When you get rich
Uh, the hair is pounding on the wall.
I went on a trip to Mt. Geumgang with my mom.
money is me
can take
Without stopping
I'm going to go
Then what happens?
I can't even go to Dr. Han.
There is no
Because you don’t know life
No, somehow
People just grow bigger today
I saw it
It's because I made a big decision.
It's not swollen.
Looks like you gained weight haha
Jisong, do you want to follow me over there?
Hit me under the streetlight over there
Looks just right
I'm going to go to karaoke.
Hey, I got caught
Look at the real song
Haha, this girl is licking it too.
Haha
Oh, he licked it so hard
Oh, that's right, you licked it earlier.
Haha what is it
Ah, when did I ride?
Oh, it's still far away
Breaking down is a habit
What kind of jackpot did the kids hit?
It's still far away
What is this
uh
Awesome
Ah, line
2004 years
I dream of three winds in the music industry
This is the stage of new singer Han Ji-woo.
I am a relative of singer Ham Ji-woo.
Oh, it was a stage.
Yes, please
uh
Find your dream
Our hard-working, brave girl
Many wishes to Dahye’s family
Please
Guys
I came, I came
Hey you
Yesterday I saw the echo of love
I saw it
Awesome, but don't be too pushy.
It was a little like that, it wasn't completely wet.
Ans, there is moisture in my eyes.
Ah haha ah
I'm embarrassed
How do you carry your face?
no
Isn't that guy really awesome?
What I'm saying is, I'm really pitiful.
When I can't even show it to my friends, ugh
I can't see it either
I really don't know what to do with him haha
What is day school?
uh class
Ah
I did my homework
You're doing the minimum.
I didn't invite you to the group chat room either.
people
I don't even want it
I will invite Jisung.
I'm just watching
Isn't it walking on the team?
our team
Why do you risk your life for a company dinner like that?
But if you want to flirt
What should I do hahaha
Doctor, are you greedy?
They said they're having a party tomorrow.
It's the perfect day to betray
On table one
Dr. Han will also sit down.
The main character is right here
Who should I be?
tomorrow event
I'm going to sit next to Dr. Han.
Just sit next to me
What is it? Why are you taking my name out?